# Sungjae Hwang

sjmini.github.io jason.sungjae.hwang@gmail.com Updated: October 13, 2021

# Research Interest

My research interests are broadly in the areas of system and software security. I use the program analysis techniques and perform vulnerability analysis to identify, understand, and alleviate security problems. My past security research covered JNI, Android, Blockchain, and Automobile domains. I also have experienced in developing system security SW adopted in automotive platform in mass production quality. For my Ph.D. degree, I research design problems and vulnerabilities in the Android platform. During my Ph.d study, I also developed automated techniques to find security issues in Android and blockchain platform.

# EDUCATION

# Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

Daejeon, KR

2018-2021

Advisor: Sukyoung RyuCo-Advisor: Yongdae Kim

Ph.D in Information Security

- Thesis: Towards Secure Interoperation in Android: A study of interoperation vulnerabilities in Android

# Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

Daejeon, KR

M.S. in Information Security

2012-2014

Advisor: Yongdae KimCo-Advisor: Sukyoung Ryu

- Thesis: Self-Update Vulnerability in Android

# University of Manchester

Manchester, UK

B.S. in Software Engineering

2005-2008

# **PUBLICATIONS**

- 1. Sungjae Hwang, Sungho Lee, Jihoon Kim, and Sukyoung Ryu, "JUSTGen: Effective Test Generation for Unspecified JNI Behaviors on JVMs", 43rd ACM/IEEE International Conference on Software Engineering (ICSE), May 2021
- 2. **Sungjae Hwang**, and Sukyoung Ryu, "Gap between Theory and Practice: An Empirical Study of Security Patches in Solidity", 42nd ACM/IEEE International Conference on Software Engineering (ICSE), May 2020
  - Tool open-source project: github.com/sjmini/icse2020-Solidity
- 3. **Sungjae Hwang**, Sungho Lee, and Sukyoung Ryu, "All about Activity Injection: Threats, Semantics, Detection, and Defense", Software: Practice and Experience (SPE), 2020.
- 4. Sungho Lee, **Sungjae Hwang**, and Sukyoung Ryu, "All about Activity Injection: Threats, Semantics, and Detection", 32st IEEE/ACM International Conference on Automated Software Engineering (ASE), November 2017
- 5. **Sungjae Hwang**, Sungho Lee, Yongdae Kim, and Sukyoung Ryu, "Bittersweet ADB: Attacks and Defenses", 10th ACM ASIA Conference on Computer and Communications Security (ASIACCS), April 2015
- 6. Sungjae Hwang, "Update Vulnerability in Android", M.S. Thesis, KAIST, 2014
- 7. Sangyong Choi, and **Sungjae Hwang**, "A Technique of Symptoms Analysis over Time for Detection of APT Attacks,", *International Conference on Smart Convergence Technologies and Applications (SCTA)*, 2012

## EXPERIENCE

SUNGKYUNKWAN UNIVERSITY Assistant Professor	Seoul, KR 2021–Present
LG Electronics, Vehicle Solutions Division, Security Team Senior Security Researcher	Seoul, KR 2017–2021
LG Electronics, Mobile Communication Division, Security Team Assistant Security Researcher	Seoul, KR 2015–2017
Korea Internet & Security Agency Assistant Security Researcher	Seoul, KR 2011–2012
ISIS Korea, Inc. Software Engineer	Seoul, KR 2008–2011

# TEACHING

- Instructor at SUNGKYUNKWAN University

  Computer Programming for Engineers
- Student Teaching Assistant at KAIST Security 101: Think Like an Adversary
- Student Teaching Assistant at KAIST Information Security Labs
- Employee Training at LG Electronics Automotive Hacking and SDL
- Employee Training at LG Electronics Software Security

# PROJECTS

# Security Analysis of Cloud Platform

2021-Present

Perform security analysis on kubernetes to find new security issues and develop tools for mitigate them

#### Runtime Checker for JNI operations

2020-Present

Design and develop a JVM independent runtime checker for unspecified JNI behaviors

#### **Automatic Generation of Access Control Rules**

2020-Present

Using program analysis techniques to automatically generate access control rules for vehicle SW

#### Development of Security SW for Vehicle Components

2017-2021

Developed Security SW adopted in LG's vehicle components such as infotainments, telematics, clusters

- Developed secure storage features using NVIDIA's TrustZone
- Developed secure boot features for binary verifications
- Developed FPM (FingerPrint Module) for user authentications
- Developed crypto services for encryption, decryption, and verifications

#### Development of Security SW for Smart Phone

2015-2017

Developed Security SW adopted in LG's smart phones

- Developed SIM Lock features using Qualcomm's TrustZone (QSEE)

- Developed SEAndroid rules for proper access control
- Developed secure communication channel between modem SW and Android SW

# Analysis of JNI Debug Features on JVMs

2019-2020

Using program analysis techniques to analyze JNI debug features on mainstream JVMs

- Developed a framework which automatically finds unspecified cases from the JNI specification using symbolic execution and generates test programs triggering unspecified cases
- Found 792 issues and 563 issues are fixed by JVM vendors
- Published work at ICSE 2021

# Analysis of Security Patches in Solidity

2018-2020

Analyzed smart contracts to understand the security levels of them and common mistakes from developers

- Developed a static analysis tool for finding vulnerabilities in smart contracts
- Found many vulnerable smart contracts
- CVE-2019-15078, CVE-2019-15079, CVE-2019-15080, CVE-2019-18775, CVE-2019-18776, CVE-2019-18777,
   CVE-2019-18778, CVE-2019-18779
- Revealed limitation of Solidity patches and common mistakes from developers
- $-\,$  Published work at ICSE 2020

# Security Analysis of Android Apps

2015-2020

Analyzed Android apps dynamically and statically to find vulnerabilities

- Developed static analysis tools for finding vulnerable apps
- Introduced new types of attacks on Android
- Found vulnerabilities from popular apps such as Skype, Yahoo Mail, Netflix, Ebay, Viber, and IMbD
- Published work at ASE, ASIACCS, SPE

# AWARDS AND ACHIEVEMENTS

• Ph.D Scholarship from LG Eletronics.	2018 – 2022
• Member of South Korea National Chess Team for Summer Universiade	2013
$\bullet$ 1 <sup>st</sup> place in Mind Sport Olympiad Chess Tournament	2010
$\bullet$ Member of South Korea National Chess Team for 38th World Chess Olympiad	2008
$\bullet$ 1 <sup>st</sup> place in Mind Sport Olympiad Chess Tournament	2008
$\bullet$ 3 <sup>rd</sup> place in Asian Dragon Chess Tournament	2008
ullet 1st place in Mind Sport Olympiad Chess Tournament	2006

#### References

# Sukyoung Ryu

Associate Professor at KAIST sryu.cs@kaist.ac.kr

# Sungho Lee

Assistant Professor at Chungnam National University eshaj@cnu.ac.kr

#### Yongdae Kim

Professor at KAIST yongdaek@kaist.ac.kr

#### Sehyeon Jang

Chief Research Engineer at LG Electronics sehyeon.jang@lge.com